let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: " Who is known as the national hero of the Philippines?",
        answer: "A. José Rizal",
        options: [
            "A. José Rizal",
            "B. Andres Bonifacio",
            "C. Emilio Aguinaldo",
            "D. Emilio Aguinaldo"

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Who is known as the Father of the Philippine Revolution?",
        answer: "B. Andres Bonifacio",
        options: [
            "A. José Rizal",
            "B. Andres Bonifacio",
            "C. Marcelo H. del Pilar",
            "D. Antonio Luna"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which national hero is often referred to as the Brains of Revolution",
        answer: "B. Apolinario Mabini",
        options: [
            "A. Emilio Aguinaldo",
            "B. Apolinario Mabini",
            "C. Marcelo H. del Pilar",
            "D. Antonio Luna"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Who was the first and the youngest president of the Philippines?",
        answer: "A. Emilio Aguinaldo",
        options: [
            "A. Emilio Aguinaldo",
            "B. Apolinario Mabini",
            "C. Antonio Luna",  
            "D. George Dewey"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Who was the first recorded hero in Philippine history?",
        answer: "D. Lapu-lapu",
        options: [
            "A. José Rizal",
            "B. Andres Bonifacio",
            "C. Antonio Luna",
            "D. Lapu-lapu"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What is the national bird of the Philippines?",
        answer: "B. Philippine Eagle",
        options: [
            "A. Maya",
            "B. Philippine Eagle",
            "C. Sarimanok",
            "D. Tamaraw"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "The national flower of the Philippines is known by what name?",
        answer: "A. Sampaguita",
        options: [
            "A. Sampaguita",
            "B. Waling-waling",
            "C. Rosal",
            "D. Gumamela"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which animal is considered the national symbol of the Philippines?",
        answer: "A. Carabao",
        options: [
            "A. Carabao",
            "B. Tarsier",
            "C. Butanding (Whale Shark)",
            "D. Dugong"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What is the national tree of the Philippines?",
        answer: "A. Narra",
        options: [
            "A. Narra",
            "B. Acacia",
            "C. Mahogany",
            "D. Molave"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: " What is the national gem of the Philippines?",
        answer: "D. Philippine Pearl",
        options: [
            "A. Diamond",
            "B. Ruby",
            "C. Emerald",
            "D. Philippine Pearl"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Which of the following is a UNESCO World Heritage Site and considered one of the new Seven Wonders of Nature in the Philippines?",
        answer: "D. Underground River in Puerto Princesa",
        options: [
            "A. Banaue Rice Terraces",
            "B. Chocolate Hills",
            "C. Mayon Volcano",
            "D. Underground River in Puerto Princesa"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "This historical site in Manila, also known as the Walled City, is a UNESCO World Heritage Site and was the seat of government during the Spanish colonial period.",
        answer: "C. Intramuros",
        options: [
            "A. Fort Santiago",
            "B. Rizal Park",
            "C. Intramuros",
            "D. Corregidor Island"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "What is the Banaue Rice Terraces?",
        answer: "A. It is a UNESCO World Heritage Site.",
        options: [
            "A. It is a UNESCO World Heritage Site.",
            "B. It is the largest rice plantation in the Philippines.",
            "C. It is a mountain range in northern Luzon.",
            "D. It is a popular beach resort."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "Where is the site of General Douglas MacArthur’s return to the Philippines?",
        answer: "A. Leyte Landing Memorial Park",
        options: [
            "A. Leyte Landing Memorial Park",
            "B. Rizal Park",
            "C. Luneta Park",
            "D. Manila Bay"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "What is the significance of the Chocolate Hills in Bohol?",
        answer: "B. They are a unique geological formation and a popular tourist attraction.",
        options: [
            "A. They are the site of a major archaeological discovery.",
            "B. They are a unique geological formation and a popular tourist attraction.",
            "C. They are the site of a historic battle.",
            "D. They are considered sacred by local indigenous communities."
        ]
    },
];